cheddar.com 2018-12-31

# Cheddar

_Effective Date:_ November 11, 2017  
_Last Updated:_ November 11, 2017  

## Overview

This is the Privacy Policy of Cheddar Inc. (Cheddar, we, or us). Cheddar provides the Cheddar Services that allows consumers like you to have access to and view our Cheddar Content. The Cheddar Content can also be accessed on our mobile Cheddar App. Any terms not defined herein shall have the meaning given to them in the associated Terms of Service available at <https://cheddar.com/terms>. 

_Types of Data We Collect:_ Personal Data means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. Anonymous Data means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below. 

## Account Security

You are solely responsible for (i) maintaining the security of your Account and (ii) all activity that occurs under your Account. You must notify us immediately if you suspect any unauthorized access to or use of your Account. If you forget your Account login information, you may request that we send it to the email address associated with your Account. 

## Information that We Collect

Cheddar, and vendors acting on Cheddar's behalf, may collect Personal Data from and about you as follows: 

_Account-related Information:_ To create an Account, you must provide certain information, including Personal Data such as your email address and a password. We may allow you to submit additional information including an avatar. You may provide other information about yourself in connection with surveys, contests, special offers, customer support inquiries, and other communications with us. 

_Usage Information:_ We collect information about your use of the Cheddar Service, including your accessing, viewing, and downloading of Cheddar Content. 

_Information Collected Automatically:_ We collect information about your use of our websites and Cheddar Apps. This may include your activities, your IP address, your browser type, your Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, your operating system or device type, date/time stamps, and related metadata. How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals. We do not currently respond to “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that might enable consumers to opt out of tracking on our website. Flash LSOs. When we post videos, third parties may use local shared objects, known as Flash Cookies, to store your preferences for volume control or to personalize certain video features. 

_Mobile Device and Services:_ If you use our services on your mobile device, including through our Cheddar App, we may collect the unique device id number. We may also collect non-personal information from your mobile device if you have downloaded our Cheddar App. This information is generally used to help us deliver the most relevant information to you. Examples of information that may be collected and used include how you use the Cheddar App, and information about the type of device you use. In addition, in the event our Cheddar App crash on your mobile device, we will receive information about your mobile device model software version and device carrier, which allows us to identify and fix bugs and otherwise improve the performance of our Cheddar App). This information is sent to us as aggregated information and is not traceable to any individual and cannot be used to identify an individual. 

## Third Party Data Collection

_Third Party Platforms:_ When you use an application that runs on a third-party platform (e.g., iOS, Roku, etc.), the provider of that third party platform may collect Personal Data or other information about you and your use of our Cheddar App. 

_Analytics and Advertising:_ We may use third party analytics services to collect data about usage of our services. We may allow third party advertising companies (including advertising agencies, networks, and delivery vendors) to collect data regarding advertisements that they may place on our websites. Third party analytics providers and advertising companies may use cookies to track your activities. Some advertising companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. 

## How We Use Your Information

Cheddar may use the information that we collect about you to: 

  * Fulfill your orders and deliver Cheddar Content and other services to you;
  * Provide customer support to you;
  * Analyze how our services are being used;
  * Communicate with you;
  * Verify your eligibility to make purchases and participate in offers;
  * Collect any debts, prevent fraud, and otherwise protect the integrity of our systems;
  * Enforce our legal rights;
  * Perform any functions described at the time of collection; and
  * Otherwise operate our business.

## Disclosures to Third Parties

Cheddar may disclose information about you as follows: 

_Authorized Service Providers:_ We may disclose your information to service providers involved in operating our business. This includes payment providers, email service providers, content delivery networks, cloud storage providers, analytics companies, and professionals such as accountants and lawyers. These service providers are required not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by Cheddar. 

_Legal Situations:_ We may disclose your information when we believe in good faith that (i) disclosure is required by a search warrant, subpoena (whether criminal or civil), civil investigative demand, court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; (ii) disclosure is appropriate and necessary to report a suspected crime (including any case of suspected child exploitation) or prevent physical harm to an individual or property; (iii) disclosure is appropriate and necessary to enforce our rights; and (iv) disclosure is required by law. Nothing in this Privacy Policy shall be deemed to create any third party right, and we reserve the right to object to any third-party requests for information in appropriate circumstances. 

_Affiliates and Corporate Transactions:_ We may disclose your information to our parent companies in connection with operating our business. In the event Cheddar or its parent companies are involved in a business transition that involves the sale, merger, or divestment of Cheddar or its parent companies, we may disclose any information about you to the acquiring entities. The transferred information will remain subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, as updated. 

_To the Public:_ We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data. We may publicly disclose Anonymous Data and aggregated user statistics and other information. 

## Emails

When you create an Account, you may receive certain emails: 

_Transaction emails:_ When you first register with Cheddar, we may send you a welcome email that provides information about the Cheddar Service and your Account. We may also, from time to time, send you other emails concerning your Account status. You may not opt-out of receiving transactional emails. 

_Newsletters:_ We may send you newsletters and other emails about new or upcoming Cheddar products, services, or offers. If you decide you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt-out as instructed in each email or in your Account settings. 

## Security Measures

We use security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent disruptions or unauthorized access from occurring. 

## Your Privacy Choices

You may choose not to provide us with certain information. If you fail to provide us with certain information, you might not be able to use certain services that we offer. 

You may change your Account information or close your Account at any time by logging into your Account and selecting Account setting. If you close your Account, you may lose access to the Cheddar Content that was available to you through your Subscription to the Cheddar Services. We may preserve your Account information (i) for a period of time in case of accidental deletion or in case you change your mind; and (ii) where we believe in good faith that preservation is required by law or necessary to enforce our rights. 

You can stop all collection of information by the Cheddar App by uninstalling the Cheddar App. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. 

## Using our Services from Outside of the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on or via our service from residents of the United States. If you are using our services from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data privacy and protection laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy, and you consent to such transfer. 

## Children's Privacy

_Consumers:_ In order to create an Account with Cheddar, an individual must be at least 13 years of age. Children older than 13 but younger than 18 must have the consent of the child's parent or guardian to use the Cheddar Service. 

If you believe that we might have any Personal Data from a child under 13, please contact us at support@cheddar.com. 

## Third Party Services

We may provide links to third party websites and applications. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or applications, or to any collection of your Personal Data after you click on links to such outside websites. We have no control over such services and therefore refer you to their privacy policies for Personal Data or other information on their respective privacy practices. The links to third party websites or locations are for your convenience and do not signify our endorsement of such third parties or their products, content or websites. 

## Security of Credit Card

For online payments of your Subscription, we use the payment services of Stripe, Inc. (https://stripe.com). We do not process, record or maintain your credit card or bank account information. For more information on how payments are handled, or to understand the data security and privacy afforded such information, please refer to https://stripe.com/us/privacy. 

## Updates

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting an updated Privacy Policy on the Cheddar website. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy at www.cheddar.com/privacy, and we will change the “Last Updated” date above. Your continued use of our services constitutes your agreement to the updated Privacy Policy on a prospective basis. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Cheddar Inc.  
1 State Street, 25th Floor  
New York, New York 10004  
Attn: Legal Dept. – General Counsel
